DJ WESTERFIELD

CONTACT INFORMATION

EMAIL: avoidthemartyr@gmail.com **WEB:** http://www.djwesterfield.com

SUMMARY

I am a web designer with an emphasis in Advertising/Marketing. Experience with HTML, PHP, MySQL 7.0, Adobe CS4, Javascript, CSS, FTP Clients (Filezilla), Wordpress 3.0, Blogspot, Google Analytics, Social Media Sites (myspace, facebook, last.fm, ning, buzznet, flickr, imeem, etc) and Cpanel.

EDUCATION

BA Degree: (2009) Philosophy

University of Redlands, Redlands, CA

Emphasis in Ethics + Chinese

RECENT PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

<u>English as a Second Language Instructor</u>, Ke Er International Montessori, Beijing, China (October 2010-Present)

<u>Web & Design Consultant</u>, Rock Steady LA, Hollywood, California (*January 2010-April 2010*)

<u>Webmaster</u>, www.modernsuperstitions.com Hollywood, California (*February 2010–April 2010*)

<u>Webmaster</u>, <u>www.makingsunlight.com</u>, Long Beach, California (*February 2010-Present*)

<u>Webmaster</u>, <u>www.theowler.com</u>, Hollywood, California (*January 2010–February 2010*)

<u>Web/Graphic Design intern</u>, Rock Steady LA, Hollywood, California (October 2009-December 2009)

<u>Webmaster/Graphic Designer</u>, Noa Noa Music, Santa Monica, California (*June 2007- September 2009*)

<u>Station Manager</u>, KDAWG Radio, Redlands, California (August 2007 - May 2009)

<u>Web/Graphic Design intern</u>, Epic Records, Santa Monica, California (*June 2008-August 2008*)

<u>Freelance Graphic Designer</u>, 31G Records, San Diego, California (*July 2007*)

Program Director, KDAWG Radio, Redlands, California
(September 2005 - May 2007)

Sound Engineer, Alliance Acoustical, Long Beach,
 California (June 2006-November 2006)
 Graphic Designer, SideCho Records, Signal Hill,
 California (May 2006-August 2006)

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- -Adobe Photoshop CS4 and below
- -Adobe Illustrator CS4 and below
- -Adobe Dreamweaver CS4 and below
- -MySQL 7.0
- -Coral Video Studio 12 and below
- -QuarkXPress 8 and below
- -MS Office 2010 and below
- -FileZilla FTP 3.3

OTHER RELEVANT SKILLS

- -Strong Photography Skills
- -Professional creation of Wordpress & Blogspot Websites
- -Music Enthusiast
- -Efficient verbal & written communication at corporate & public level
- -Expert level in creating social network layouts (Myspace, Imeem, Buzznet, Ning, etc)

PUBLICATIONS

2008 (Fall) Redlands Review, University of Redlands 2008 (November) Artistic Autopsy Magazine

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.

THANKS FOR READING!
HOPE TO TALK SOON
avoidthemartyr@gmail.com

